http://www.aakkamani.com/privacy-policy.aspx#pagesec

Terms of Sale
Copyright 2018 AAK KAMANI Pvt. Ltd. All Rights Reserved.
Global : AAK.com
Introduction:
We, AAK Kamani Private Limited understand the importance of maintaining privacy and thus abide by the highest standards to secure customer information privacy. We appreciate the trust that you have in us.
This Privacy Policy distinctly informs our users about the type of information we collect from our users, the reason for collecting such information, how we intend on using such information and the choices available to our customers regarding our use of such information. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.
Please read our Policy carefully to understand how we treat the information provided by you. By clicking on the “Accept” button, you will agree to the collection, use, disclosure, retention and protection of your Personal Information as provided in this Policy. However, if you do not consent to any of the terms enumerated in this Policy, you may choose not to use our services by clicking on the “Decline” button. However, please be aware that if you do not allow us to collect the Personal Information as enumerated in this Policy, we may not be able to provide you with certain services.
Information we collect:
For a more interactive platform and advanced efficiency in our services, we may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information such as Name, Gender, Date of Birth, User name, Password, Email ID, Mobile No., Postal address, Security Question, Answer, Organisation Name and Address, Date of Anniversary, Area or segment of business, browsing history, preferences and IP address. The information that we request will be retained by us and used as described in this Privacy Policy.
How we use this information:
We collect this Personal Information directly from you when you provide it to us. Since our platform is interactive, we use this information for purposes such as:
Improving our services;
Communicating with you;
Processing and responding to your queries
Informing you about the existing and new products launched by us;
Informing you about new upcoming events organized by us;
Sending you information about special promotions or offers;
Engaging in an interactive session to discuss and exchange ideas related to cooking recipes;
Contacting you for promotional purposes;
Providing you with customer support;
Allowing you to participate in interactive features offered through our services;
Conducting various programmes such as the Karigar Connect program, expert exchange program;
Booking appointments to visit our customer innovation centre;
Registering for events / workshops/seminars;
Providing information on company and industry updates and updates on global business;
In any other way we may describe when you provide the information;
For any other purpose, with your consent;
Cookies
We may track your preferences and activities on our mobile application and/ or website. By accepting this Privacy Policy, you agree to our use of cookies. If you do not agree to our use of cookies, you can block them in your browser setting, however, some of our services may not function properly if you disable cookies.
With whom we share The Personal Information:
We may have to share your Personal Information with third parties for fulfilling the afore-said purposes.
We require such third parties to respect the security of the Personal Information provided by us and to treat the same in accordance with the applicable law.
How long will we retain your Personal Information?
We shall retain the Personal Information provided by you for only as long as it is necessary for the purposes set out in this Policy, for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide the services to you.
Keep in mind that even though our systems are designed to carry out deletion of information as per the above guidelines, we are not liable for the non-deletion of certain data within a specific time frame due to technological constraints.
Opt-Out:
If you do not wish to receive any promotional or marketing communications or otherwise from us or if you do not wish your information to be processed by us, you can contact us at +91 18002666363+91 18002666363 or email Us at info.in@aakkamani.com in order to opt out from receiving such communications.
Rectification or Erasure of information:
You are entitled to contact us at +91 18002666363+91 18002666363 or email Us at info.in@aakkamani.com to request for rectification of the Personal Information collected by us and/ or for erasure of your Personal Information.
Withdrawal of Consent:
If you have given your free consent to the collection, use, disclosure, retention and protection of your Personal Information, and wish to withdraw such consent, you may do so by contacting us at +91 18002666363+91 18002666363 or email Us at info.in@aakkamani.com
at any time.
Notwithstanding the above provisions, any decision by you to opt-out, rectify or erase information from our records or withdraw your consent shall not in any manner whatsoever affect and/ or make illegal the processing of your information done prior to the communication of your afore-said decision to us.
You agree and acknowledge that we shall not be liable for disclosure of Personal Information which may be required under the law and/ or order of any court and / or authority.
You further acknowledge that we shall not be responsible in any manner whatsoever to verify the authenticity of the information provided by you to us.
Child Protection Policy:
We do not collect such personally identifiable information from children. If you are legally considered a child, do not provide us with any such personal data.
If we have mistakenly collected such Personal Information from a child, we shall have the same deleted immediately when brought to our notice.
If you are a parent or a guardian and are aware that your child has provided us with such information, kindly contact us at +91 18002666363+91 18002666363 or email Us at info.in@aakkamani.com, to have such information deleted immediately.
Confidentiality & Proprietary Rights
You acknowledge that
our website and / or mobile application shall contain information and/ or content and/ or works which are confidential and proprietary to us and that You shall not disclose and/ or use in any manner and/ or reproduce such information and/ or content and/ or works and/ or any part thereof without our prior written consent.
You further acknowledge that you shall not in any manner replicate and/ or imitate and/ or reproduce and/ or use in part or otherwise, our intellectual property including but not limited to trade marks, logos, domain names, trading name, designs, concepts, images, diagrams, drawings, business methods, trade secrets, patents, copyright etc. without a written license duly executed by us.
Security:
We strictly adhere to high standards to ensure that your Personal Information is kept secured. We endeavor to keep your Personal Information up-to-date and accurate in the best possible manner as it may be necessary for the purpose for which it was collected, used, retained and disclosed. We highly value the significance of your Personal Information shared with us and have thus, (i) taken all reasonable measures and precautions to keep such information safe and secure and to prevent any unauthorized access to or misuse of the same; and (ii) enable you to review and edit the same.
However, we shall not be liable to any user for any loss, damage (whether direct, indirect, consequential or incidental) or harm caused to the user due to the unauthorized access or misuse of the Personal Information by any third party.
In all events, you shall be solely responsible to protect and keep secure your password and/ or details required to access your account maintained by you on this app and/ or website.
Indemnity
You agree and undertake to indemnify, keep indemnified, defend and hold us harmless in any suit or dispute initiated against us by any Third Party arising out of disclosure of Personal Information by You to Third Parties either through Our Website, mobile application or otherwise and / or the authenticity of such personal information and/ or Your use and access of websites, applications and resources of Third Parties. We assume no liability for any actions of Third Parties in relation to Your Personal Information and/ or use by them of such Personal Information, which You may have disclosed to such Third Parties.
Changes in Privacy Policy:
We may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You are responsible for periodically reviewing this Policy in order to be aware of any changes thereto. Your continued use of our services subsequent to such change in Policy constitutes your acceptance of such changed Policy and your approval to be bound by such changes.
Contact Us:
If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us at +91 18002666363+91 18002666363 or email Us at info.in@aakkamani.com
